Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Move! Move! Get out of the way!
Move!
Stay with me, Rose, all right?
Stay with me. Come on.
- Hey, hey, hey, look, look at me!
- When it all falls apart...
...you can surrender on sight.
- Locked it.
- You can run for the exits...
...or you can fight back...
...to your last breath...
...until there's nothing left.
L.A.P.D. Metro.
Third one today.
- Hey, Mark.
- How are you, doll?
- Good to see your face around here.
- Mm-hm.
- You coming back to work soon?
- Yeah, any day.
- Actually, I'm...
- Hey! If it isn't Old Glory Corley.
- All right, man. Oh.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Give me a hug. Give me a hug.
- How you doing?
- Good, man. He all right?
- Come on.
- Good to see ya.
- You look worse than I imagined.
- What the hell you imagining me for?
- Sorry to drag you down here, man.
- No one else gives a shit, right?
Well, at least he's got you.
Poor bastard.
There he is...
...resting comfortably.
You son of a bitch.
Lock him up.
- You're serious?
- Mm-hm.
You let him out,
I'll kill him myself, lock him up.
This is his third offense, Mark.
I process him, he's in for a lot more
than an over-nighter.
- All right.
- Look...
...I know it's been tough
on both of you since Rose passed.
Yeah.
I talked to the other guy.
He's not gonna press charges.
This is the last time
I can help you out, man.
- Well, I appreciate it.
- All right.
That's what partners do.
It's nice to see you out and about, Mark,
get that fresh air and shit.
Just get in the fucking truck, smart ass.
- Do you even wanna hear my side?
- Why?
This ends with you in jail, don't it?
You wanna piss your life away,
son, that's on you.
At least have the balls to own it, for once.
- I'll get the jumpers.
- It's not the battery.
Jeez.
Can we call a cab?
- You got money for that?
- How much was that whiskey?
Change.
Here you go.
V.A. don't give a fuck.
Nobody does, brother.
Change.
Next stop, Fifth and Flower.
You are so much smarter than this.
Christ knows you didn't get that from me.
But this whole, "Fuck the world," routine,
it's just not working for ya.
Some people got it coming.
That's your words, not mine.
My words, wise ass,
my words don't put me in lock-up.
He said some shit...
...it deserved an answer, all right, so I...
- ...I hit him once.
- One time?
You broke his jaw with one punch?
It fucking connected.
Nice.
I don't know what I'm gonna do with you.
Change.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Everyone all right?
What the hell was that?
87 westbound, can you hear me?
This is 87 westbound, can you hear me?
- Yes, how can I help you, sir?
- Audrey, what seems to be the problem?
Power outage... the radio's down. It takes
a few minutes to get the system back up.
Even without the power the radio should work.
I know that, but it doesn't.
This is 87 westbound, can you hear me?
I'm not trying to step on your toes here,
it's just I don't like tight spaces...
- ...so if there's anything I can do...
- You'll be the first to know. Thanks.
Okay.
This is eight...
What the hell was that?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Shut this door.
- Please stay calm. No one's leaving the train.
- Officer, please.
- I got two kids at home.
I wanna get home too, okay?
But this is procedure to keep you all safe.
Please sit. Sit.
This is 87 westbound. Can you hear me?
Don't look to the lights. Just don't look!
87 westbound, can you hear me? Over.
- Don't look at the lights.
- Light, what light?
Fuck procedure. Move! Move!
- Here, here.
- Okay. Okay.
- Everyone all right?
- Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
- Bring 'em out. To the right.
- Make a single file to the right.
Don't run. Just follow the person
in front of you, and please stay calm.
Listen to what she's telling you.
All right. Okay.
- Please, stay to the right.
- To the right. Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow.
Okay. Okay.
Come on, follow me.
- Please stay to the right.
- Come on, Trent.
Come on.
What the hell is that, huh?
Move!
Yeah.
Keep moving! Keep moving, please.
Watch these rails.
Jones. Where the fuck is everybody?
I don't know.
Where you all going?
Hold up.
Hey!
Trent! Hey!
What the...
Whoa, hold up!
Come on.
Stay behind me, all right?
Hey, hold on one second.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- I gotta get to my kids.
- You don't even know what that is.
Hey. Hey, hey! Excuse me.
Hey. What are you doing? Stop. Excuse me.
Hey, what the... Mark! Mark!
Mark!
Mark. Oh, my God, the light. Mark!
Don't look at the light! This is what
they were trying to warn us about!
Trent! Put your head down! Trent!
Trent!
Trent, don't look up!
Damn it! Trent!
Mark!
Holy shit!
- Mark, are you okay?
- Up! Up!
What the hell is going on up there?
- Trent, you gotta breathe. Trent, breath!
- Hey! Hey, hey!
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- Move! Move!
Go, go, go! Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
We're under attack.
What the hell you think that was,
terrorists or what, huh?
- ISIS doesn't have no fucking spaceship!
- Look at me, son.
- What was that?
- Look at me.
- I have no idea.
- You must have seen something.
I can't explain it. There was
a light shot out of a cannon.
- A cannon?
- It took everyone.
- Trent! Come on, son. Breathe.
- I need to see his eyes.
- Come on, son. Breathe. Come on, breathe.
- Okay. He's lucid. Get him up.
- On three. One, two, three.
- It's okay. Come on.
We can't go back to the train.
We gotta get to the station house.
- Get up, there.
- You got him?
Come on. I got him.
Whoa!
- Garcia?
- Son of a bitch!
So I come out of the crapper
and the whole station's cleared out.
Okay, not just empty,
more like everyone just vanished.
And this blue light came in the street.
That's when we saw it.
Oh, my God, this is really happening.
Full scale. Christ.
Give me that gun.
- You got clips?
- Yeah.
- All right. We keep moving. Let's go.
- No, you're not hearing me, brother.
- There's nowhere else to go.
- We move or we die. Let's go. Now.
- Tracks only go as far as Koreatown!
- You wanna stay here, fine. We move.
Guys, can you put your dicks away?
They're building a new extension on this line.
- Tunnel goes all the way to the west side.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- It's safe?
I don't know, but I think it's worth a shot.
All right. We make our way
to the water, we find the military.
Find the Marines, something.
We just keep moving. Let's go.
- Guess we're moving.
- Let's do it.
- Come on.
- Everybody stay close.
Hey, you need help, old man?
Give me your hand.
I'm... I'm Sarge.
Nice to meet you, Sarge.
I'm Trent. Come on.
Fucking aliens, man.
Are we almost there?
Been walking all night.
Hold on. We're at a service shack.
You're gonna step up, there's a step here,
all right. I'm going to go in front of you.
- Watch it.
- You got it.
- You see this?
- Yeah.
- Here we go.
- Check it out.
- What do you see up there, man?
- Check that radio.
Ten-nine-nine. This is L.A.P.D.
Oh, shit.
Ten-nine-nine. This is L.A.P.D., acknowledge.
Planes! They're ours.
- They're ours.
- Acknowledging.
Requesting extraction.
Three officers, four civilians.
Negative extraction.
Proceed to marina, Basin H.
- Come again on that.
- Clear the city as fast as you can!
They're going after that ship.
Move! Move down! Go. Go!
Move! Go, go, go, move!
Move out of the way! Move, move! Run, run!
I got you!
Sarge? You all right?
Shit.
Everybody okay? Jones?
Yeah.
Shit.
They're dead.
They fucking nuked L.A.
Blast like that got to be tactical.
Short range, low yield.
You can tell that just from listening?
Otherwise we'd all be dead.
Only one way out.
Come on.
Hey! Don't look!
Trent! Trent! Goddamn it!
Goddamn it.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Fine. Yeah.
Get me out of here!
All right! All right!
You gotta be kidding me. All right, come on.
Shit.
Are you all right?
I'm okay. I could breathe
in there and everything.
Maybe it wanted you alive.
Move! Move!
It ripped her fucking brain out! We gotta go!
There's a car. We're going up, okay?
Sarge, climb on the wheel. Sarge, come on!
Go! Go!
- Dad!
- Move! Go! Move!
That's it. You got it! Come on, you two!
Come on. Come on.
- Catch!
- Dad, just grab my hand!
Motherfucker!
Go! Move! Move!
Mark!
Go!
Holy shit. You killed it.
Yeah, everything fucking burns.
Amen to that.
Oh, shit. What the...
- Move.
- Oh, my God.
- What the fuck is that?
- You don't wanna know.
Move!
- Run!
- Move!
Come on. Come on!
Hey, follow me! Come this way. Come on!
Look, find an opening! Look! There's one.
Come on, come on, through here. From the
pipe we can go in and we can go back...
- No! We're not going back in the tunnels.
- Guys! He's losing a lot of blood.
I'm okay.
Move! Move, move, move, move.
- Move!
- I can't!
No, come on! Come on!
- End of the line, Old Glory.
- What?
I'll buy you some time.
Get your kid out of here. Go!
- Garcia.
- Go!
Hola, puta.
Oh, shit!
L.A.P.D. inbound Boat Basin H.
L.A.P.D. inbound Boat Basin H. Over.
- L.A.P.D. inbound Boat Basin H. Over.
- This is a dead end.
Copy L.A.P.D. Hold your position. Over.
Hey! What's that?
Move. Move!
We gotta run.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on. Come on.
Trent.
Trent!
No!
Come and get me, motherfucker!
You bitches ain't leaving me.
Trent.
Trent. Hey. Trent.
- Huh?
- Hey.
- Trent!
- Mark!
No!
- Mark.
- Get down!
Trent!
Mark! Mark! No!
I got you.
No!
Son of a bitch.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, God.
I need a drink.
Oh, fuck.
Hey! Wait!
Hey, Audrey. Come...
Hey. Hey.
Hey, wake up. Audrey.
- Oh, my God. Where are we?
- I have no idea.
Do you have a light?
Please tell me you have a light.
Yeah. There was a flare in my back pocket.
- Fuck.
- I can't...
- I can't move my arms.
- Right.
- Other back pocket, slick.
- Sorry.
- Don't look at me like that.
Sorry.
What is... what is this place?
Wait!
Stop!
My son. I have to find my son.
He's in here somewhere. He's alive.
He's alive.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no, no.
No, no. Okay.
Wait.
Oh, you mother...
Please! Help me!
My water broke.
I think I'm in labor.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay. You're okay.
You're okay. Look at me. Breathe.
- I can't do this.
- Yes, you can! Yes, you can.
- I'm not ready.
- Look at me. Look at me.
- Just breathe and relax. Breathe. I'm a cop.
- No, you don't understand.
I've done this. Breathe!
I'm not due for another six months.
After we saw the light,
I could feel the baby growing inside me.
But Jarrod was different.
Each time, he... he grew stronger...
- ...like he became immune.
- Elaine, no! Stop!
Jarrod? No!
But they still ripped him apart.
They take our minds.
They use them to drive these... machines.
And the babies, they take them, too.
They tried to take mine...
...but he saved us.
Somehow... he came back.
Jarrod?
- Holy shit.
- Oh. Oh, God.
- Okay, okay, okay, breathe.
- It's coming.
Look, look, look, stay with me!
Stay with me, stay with me. Look in my eyes.
- What's your name?
- Elaine.
Elaine, okay. I'm Mark. I'm Mark.
Okay? We're gonna do this together.
Okay, breathe, breathe, breathe.
Almost got it. Now!
Be careful... Jesus!
I got you. I got you.
We gotta swing.
Toward that ledge, okay? Come on.
Come on. Let's do it.
This is what we're gonna go. I'm gonna
count to three and you're gonna push, okay?
One, two, three. Push! Push!
Reach! Come on! Come on.
You can do it. Reach!
Good girl, good girl.
One more time. Big push. Yeah?
- Yeah.
- One, two, three...
- ...push!
- Come on.
Just reach it. Come on! Reach!
- Got it!
- Good.
Good girl! Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Good girl. It's a little girl.
It's a... it's a little girl.
Reach, come on!
- When I catch it, you gotta let me go, okay?
- Wait, no! Why?
- Yeah, it's the only way. Come on.
- All right.
Now!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
This is yours.
Okay. I'm gonna make you a deal.
You help me find my son...
...and I promise you on my life...
...I'll get your daughter
off this ship, okay?
Okay, good.
Good. Good idea!
Okay. Your turn.
Hey, you're gonna get us killed, kid.
Jesus Christ.
What the...
What? You want me to put my arm in there?
Jesus.
Things are looking up, kid.
Are we gonna blow the ship?
Do you think that's a good idea?
Okay. Let's just take it slow, okay?
Help! Anybody there?
- Sarge, is that you?
- Sarge?
I thought I heard friendlies up there.
- Sarge, wait! Hold up!
- Take your time, kid.
This bitch ain't got nothing on Hanoi.
I know this. I've seen this.
That's their cannon.
Where's my son?
You find him?
Oh, shit.
Compared to Vietcong,
we'll be in the tiger cage.
You're okay, you're a tough kid.
Mark! Mark! Up here!
Trent.
The stubborn son of a bitch.
Hey! Hey, boy! You can save
the happy reunion for later.
You better get me down quick!
Hang in there, Sarge. We got you!
You stay put, kid. Okay.
Come on.
Oh, shit.
- Sarge, hang on!
- Hey! That don't sound good!
- What are you doing?
- He's not gonna make it.
Trent.
- Trent, come on!
- Hey!
- Hurry that shit up!
Don't you do it!
Trent!
I'm gonna get you out of here, Sarge.
If you ask me,
you ain't got to be no fucking hero!
Swing!
Come on.
- Come on!
- Hey, boy!
Get my ass out of here!
Don't let go!
Sarge, grab the ledge!
I got it! I'm on it!
Trent, look out!
Oh, fuck!
Hold on!
- Audrey!
- Trent!
- Dad!
- Look at me! Stay with me!
- Trent!
Save her.
No! No!
Mark!
Audrey!
The baby!
Holy shit.
Oh, my God!
Come on. You fucking thing.
Sarge! The baby!
Hey!
Bring it on, bitch!
Mark!
Back! Get back!
Hold on!
Come on!
Wait! Get back!
Kenya, come on!
Are you okay?
- Yeah. The baby?
- Yeah.
She's grown.
Mark, where did you find her?
I'll explain.
Not the kid.
Sarge.
What if we deserved this?
Shit.
I've more than earned it...
...but not the kid.
We have to go.
I'm so sorry, Mark.
Sarge?
Help me up.
River. Thirty feet down.
- You got to be kidding.
- Nope.
- You know I'm blind, right?
- Yeah. You're the lucky one.
There's a narrow ledge, okay?
So lift your foot.
Wait for me. Okay, you got it.
- Shit.
- Okay, ready?
Let's go.
Kanya!
Kanya! Kanya!
- Hey.
- Take the baby. Take the baby.
Okay. It's okay.
Come on, big man. That's okay.
Come on. Come on. I got you.
All right, I got you, man.
You made it, brother.
You made it, brother. No.
- What...
- No, no.
No, no, no! No, no, no, no.
- Please, please.
- Okay, he's hurt. He's hurt. All right?
Please. Help.
Do exactly as I say.
Or we leave you here. Move.
Yeah.
It's okay.
Hey? Excuse me?
The baby needs dry clothes.
Hurry up.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- I'm gonna change her.
- Okay.
It's okay.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Let her go.
All right. All right. All right. All right.
- Police. I should have fucking guessed.
- Golden Triangle.
- I already knew. We're good.
- What the hell does that mean?
Nothing. Now just get the baby, just get...
Motherfucker.
- Come on, you little boy.
- Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Mark!
Sua!
The baby.
Who are they? Warlords? Militia?
Worse... police.
Since the aliens came,
they've been on the warpath.
They take everything... the women, too.
We need to get out of this valley.
Look, I'll help you.
You... you get that baby to a doctor, yeah?
Fuck.
Oy!
Minefield.
No shortcuts in Lao.
She needs to rest.
We camp here.
When I was up on that ship...
...I only saw one real alien.
All the rest were just slaves.
Bullshit.
You love your brother, right? No matter what?
No matter what.
Well, these things are still human...
...up here.
Our family, our friends, our brothers.
If one of 'em can be freed,
they all can be freed.
It's not bullshit.
What was her name?
- I'm so sorry. Sorry.
- No. How's the kid?
She's still growing, Mark.
Yeah, I know.
I mean, what, you think they can help?
You got a better plan, let me know.
Right, okay.
Rose...
...my wife's name was Rose.
That's a classic.
She was.
What?
I don't know what you're saying.
I don't know what...
Hey! Hey, hey, no, it's okay. He's down.
He's wounded. He can't hurt you.
We'll take him with us, so please, please...
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay, okay? Okay, come here.
It's beautiful.
Wat Shiva.
A thousand years ago,
we built this to honor the gods.
Now, we use it to fight them.
Jesus Christ.
I hope they have room service.
Fucking Temple of Doom.
Harper.
- Mark.
- Nice to meet you.
What is this place?
Home.
How's it up there?
- Not good.
- Yeah, it's pretty fucked, right?
She's got an extremely high temperature.
- What is she, three years old?
- Try two days.
Yeah. They don't cover this
at med school, huh?
Actually, love, I'm a scientist.
Let me guess, a chemist by trade.
Well, it pays better than the CDC.
Plus, you really can't beat the benefits.
We need to talk.
Tell me about the girl.
What you see in there,
that's what I know, that's it.
You think I care you're police?
You think that matters now?
Some shit matters.
You hear me? Some shit still matters,
like who I can trust.
I can't trust that guy.
Drug runners aren't real high on my list.
As soon as Americans stop buying...
...we stop making.
Well, I guess the apocalypse
wasn't a total loss, then, was it?
Apocalypse. Yeah, that's funny.
Look around. When do you think
this place was built?
40 years ago you bombed us.
You tried to destroy us.
But we survived the American apocalypse.
We'll survive this one, too.
I've got a present for you.
I've never seen anything quite like this.
- Mm-hm.
- Something changed her DNA.
Change how?
I don't know if she's human.
Fuck me.
- Hey, hey. Hey! Kanya! Hey, Kanya!
- She's not welcome here!
Hey, hey, hey! Enough!
Enough! Enough! Enough, enough!
- Alien!
- No alien!
- No!
- Enough!
Listen to me. When I was on that ship...
...I saw them doing experiments on
our unborn children, dissecting them.
Unborn babies.
When women see that light, something
happens. The babies grow fast...
...most of them die.
She lived.
This child can be the key to freeing
the others. Do you understand me?
Hope. She's our hope!
Now, I've got good news and bad.
Her cell walls are denser,
almost like a shielding.
Her blood is...
nothing short of extraordinary.
Yeah, right. Okay, good. What's the bad news?
She's running out.
The constant growth has just
depleted her entire system...
...and she's shutting down...
...she needs a transfusion.
Oka... okay, but she's... she's not human.
How can we match her blood type?
I'm not gonna lie. Odds are we can't.
Hey! What about me?
I was weaponized.
How ya doing there, kiddo?
Hey.
- Well, I'll be damned.
- Yeah.
So, this is actually a bullet...
...and this blue shit is what fuels
their light weapons...
...mind control, all of it.
Can you make a vaccine?
Well, it's not actually a virus.
It behaves like bacteria, a virus...
...a sentient being, the whole gamut.
Scientifically speaking, it's, uh...
...completely bloody alien. Except...
...it's biologically compatible with our DNA.
Do you realize how unlikely that is?
They've been here before.
I'll go one further.
They might have put us here...
...planted us like a crop.
And every couple of millennia,
they come back to harvest.
Huh.
You sure he's not doing the drugs?
But...
...they weren't counting on one thing.
Evolution.
Her serum blocks it.
So, we load one of their bullets
with her blood...
...into the right delivery system...
...we can free them all.
We need to use one of their cannons.
You are not fucking around.
Wow.
Okay.
Huh?
Are you compensating for something?
Too big?
Kanya, go rig the hillside.
Take her with you.
Okay.
'Kay.
This is all we'll have for the next 24 hours.
We leave at nightfall.
Fights. Guns. Bombs.
Yeah, you're really good for my health.
Hey...
...thanks.
Stay here.
Kanya. I said...
Kanya, come in.
Kanya?
Kanya!
Duck!
What? What's wrong? What?
- The minefield!
- Oh, my God.
Oh!
Run, baby, run. Run. Run!
Whoa, what is she doing?
Run!
What?
No, No, Kanya, please. Please.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Hey, you okay?
All right, all right, all right, all right.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, breathe.
You're good. Hey, we gotta leave.
No.
We defend these tunnels every day.
Don't move. Hey!
- How much time can you give me?
- Not a lot.
I need that syringe.
- I'm going after the cannon.
- You'll never make it.
- They're still human inside.
- No! They're death.
- It's us or them.
- One of them is my son.
Yeah, it's crazy. I need the syringe.
Fucking Americans.
I'm gonna get you to someplace safe, huh?
Make sure nothing happens to you,
because I made a promise.
You know what that means?
That means that no matter what happens...
...I'm not gonna let anything hurt you.
Promise?
Yeah, kid. I promise.
Mark, you are not going out there alone.
- There's no time for this. We don't have time.
- We need to talk about this now.
We both know this is a one-way trip.
You are all she has left.
- You're the parent, Mark. Not me.
- Come on.
I'm so sorry your family is gone...
...but killing yourself
is not gonna change that.
I gotta go.
Be ready.
Ready.
They're in.
Hold.
Now!
Move back. Move back!
Give it to me.
Come on.
Oh, fuck!
All right.
Take it.
Take it. Come on.
Harper.
Apologies, love.
I'm, uh, I'm not a warrior.
I'm, uh, I'm a survivor.
I used to think that was enough.
Keep your eyes closed.
Run, run, run. Come on.
Trent? Trent!
Trent, don't!
Audrey!
Oh!
Dad! No!
Dad!
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, my God.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey, hey!
It's Trent.
Take it.
All you.
Here, here, here!
Fight, Trent! Fight!
No!
Fucking aliens.
Get out of the way, kid!
Look out!
Hey.
I told you we would survive.
Survive? We did a hell of a lot more
than survive, my friend.
We evolved.
We have a name for this little one?
How about... Rose?
Yeah.
Rose.
And that's my name.
Classic, huh?
- Captain on deck!
- At ease, guys.
That was the day we found their weakness.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Trent. I was a little busy.
And our strength.
How about next time I drive...
you get stabbed.
Now, we're not just fighting back.
We're taking the fight to them.
Ready?
Promise?
Whoa!
Fuck.
- What are you doing here?
- Just... acting and shit.
I gotta take a piss.
It ain't funny.
I'm an arm or two shorter, bro.
Bring it on!
Yeah, I can see.
- Let's get together after this.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- I'll see you on the next project.
- Yeah. Thank you.
- Okay. You, too.
You guys are...
You're the stupidest fucking monster
I've ever seen in my life.
- Fuck off.
- I'm just saying.
You're gonna blow us up.